luckstock.com 2019-12-16

# LuckStock Privacy Statement

##  WE RESPECT YOUR PRIVACY **· We don't share your private data with third-parties.

· We don't spam our users.

· We keep your private data secure.

**

Effective on 19 June, 2018

This privacy statement describes how LuckStock, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Website: www.LuckStock.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We collect the following personal information from you

1.      Contact Information such as your name and email address and other contact details.

2.      Limited Billing Information such as organization title, full address and only last four digits of your credit card numbers. We do not have access to your entire credit card numbers and other billing information processed either by Braintree credit card processing or by PayPal. You may want to check privacy policies of these credit card processing companies for more information.

3.      Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, encrypted password and IP address.

4.      Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences.

5.      The most common types of information including your profile picture and social network ids, survey responses, transactional details, tax information, support queries, content you make available on our Website (such as item descriptions) and web-analytics data.

**How we collect personal information**

1\. We collect personal information directly when you provide it to us, automatically as you navigate through our Website, or through other people hired or involved to fulfil your project when you or they use services provided by our Website.  
2\. We collect your personal information when you provide it to us, when you complete membership registration, buy or provide content or services on our Website, subscribe to a newsletter, email list, submit feedback, fill out a survey, or send us a communication.

**Personal information we collect about you from others**

  1. Although we generally collect personal information directly from you, on occasion, we also collect certain categories of personal information about you from other sources. In particular: 
    * financial and/or transaction details from payment providers
    * if you have hired or ordered a third-party to fulfil the project on your behalf and require them to provide you the license certificate and/or sales receipt indicating your name and/or billing details
    * third-party service providers (like Google, Facebook) which may provide information about you when you link, connect, or login to your account with the third-party provider and they send us your personal information such as your profile from that service. The information varies and is controlled by that service provider or as authorized by you via your privacy settings at that service provider; and
    * other third party sources/ and or partners whereby we receive additional information about you in extent to permitted by applicable law, such as fraud detection information, and combine it with information we have about you. We also receive information about you and your activities through partnerships, or about your experiences and interactions from our partner ad networks. We also receive information about you as a rights holder from our third party authors.

**How we use personal information**

As is true of most web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to

1.      Operating and improving the Website, e.g. conducting technical analysis to determine how to improve the Website and fix the issues

2.      Providing you with services described on the Website

3.      Verifying your identity

4.      Fulfill your order

5.      Send you an order confirmation

6.      Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products

7.      Send you requested product or service information

8.      Respond to customer service requests and helping facilitate the resolution of any disputes

9.      Administer your account

10.  Send you a newsletter

11.  Updating you with news and information about Website and service updates, changes, etc.

12.  Display content based upon your interests

13.  Monitoring activity on the Website to identify potential fraudulent activity or security issues and to ensure compliance with the user terms that apply to the Website

14.  In purposes required by law

15.  For the purpose of responding to requests by government, a court of law, or law enforcement authorities conducting an investigation

**Where you give us consent:**

1\. Providing you with marketing information about products and services which we feel may interest you;  
2\. Customizing the Website, our services and advertising involving cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you a more personalized experience.

**Information Obtained from Third Parties**

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

**PayPal**

If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Website.

**When we disclose your personal information**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may also disclose your personal information

1.      as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process

2.      when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,

3.      if LuckStock, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

4.      subcontractors and service providers in connection with the ways we use the personal information

5.      our professional advisers (lawyers, accountants, etc.)

6.      regulators and government authorities in connection with our compliance procedures and obligations

7.      to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

**Where we store your personal information**

We store your information on servers located in the US and Netherlands. Some of the recipients we have described above and to whom we disclose your personal information are based in countries like Ukraine, Georgia, Poland, UK and the US. We do this on the basis of your consent to this policy. In order to protect your information, where possible, we take care where possible to work with subcontractors and service providers that are taking data security seriously and maintain acceptable standard of data security compliance.

**Security of your personal information**

The security of your personal information is important to us and store personal information on secure servers that are managed by us and our service providers.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Occasional hard copies and backups are kept in a secure location in Netherlands and the US. Personal information that we store or transmit is protected by security and access controls, including username and password authentication and data encryption where appropriate.

If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us at security@LuckStock.com.

**Accessing your personal information**

You can access some of the personal information that we collect about you by logging in to your account. You also have the right to make a request to access other personal information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that data. You can also close the account you have on our Website at any time by emailing us. To request an access or ask for correction, contact our privacy coordinator using the contact details at the end of this policy.

**Marketing communication choices**

Based on your consent (e.g. if you have subscribed to one of our e-mail lists or have indicated that you are interested in receiving offers or information from us), we may send you marketing communications by email about our products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. To stop receiving the marketing communication in the future you should use the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in the communication itself.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site. For example, we will use third-party advertising companies to serve ads based on prior visits to our Website.

You also have choices about cookies by modifying your browser preferences. You have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject cookies some parts of our Website may not work properly for you.

For more general information on cookies, see http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

**Web beacons**

Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

**Information about children**

Our Website is not suitable for children under the age of 16 years, so if you are under 16 we ask that you do not use our website or give us your personal information without the prior supervisory of responsible adult. If you are from 16 to 18 years, you can browse the Website but you will need the supervision of a parent or guardian to become a registered user. It is the responsibility of parents or guardians to monitor their children’s use of our Website.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of LuckStock, Inc. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

**Information you make public or give to others**

We cannot control or accept responsibility for the personal information you make available to other people. There are lots of ways that you can find yourself providing information to other people, like when you comment on a published item, post a public message on a forum thread, share information via social media, or make contact with another user whether via our Website or directly via email. Before making your information publicly available or giving your information to anyone else, think carefully. If you are considering giving information to another user via our Website, ask them how they will handle your information. If you are sharing information via another website, check the privacy policy for that site to understand its information management practices as this privacy policy will not apply.

**How long your personal information will be kept**

To provide the services to you and others and to comply with our legal obligations, we will retain your personal information for as long as necessary. You may request to close your account and erase your personal information, though we will retain information from deleted accounts as necessary for our legitimate business interests, to comply with the law, prevent fraud, collect fees, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with investigations, enforce the terms of service and take other actions permitted by law. The information we retain will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Additional Policy Information**

Our Website includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. chat support, displaying the news, opinions etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

Our Website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

For the purposes of applicable EU data protection law (including the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the “GDPR”), we are a “data controller” of your personal information.

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at contact@LuckStock.com.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on the Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**

You can contact us about this Privacy Statement by writing or email us at the address below:  

LuckStock Inc.  
304 S. Jones Blvd, Suite 295  
Las Vegas, NV 89107

Email: [privacy@LuckStock.com](mailto:privacy@LuckStock.com)
